
=== LetterCounter ===
Input: This is a test of the letter count function
Enter a string: Number of letters in the string: 35

=== CharacterCounter ===
Input: this is a test of the character counter function
Character to count: c
Enter a string: Enter a character to count: Number of times 'c' appears in the string: 4

=== MaxIntegerFinder ===
Number of integers: 5
Integers: 10, 5, 8, 9, 11
Enter the number of integers: Enter the integers:
The maximum integer in the array is: 11

=== DigitCounter ===
Input integer: 123124125123
Digit to count: 2
Enter an integer: Enter a digit to count: Number of times digit '2' appears in the integer: 4

=== StringReverser ===
Input: This is a test of the String Reverser
Enter a string: Reversed string: resreveR gnirtS eht fo tset a si sihT

=== EvenSumCalculator ===
Number of integers: 4
Integers: 1, 3, 4, 2
Enter the number of integers: Enter the integers:
The sum of all even numbers in the array is: 6
